yourinvestmentpropertymag.com.au 2019-12-11

# Privacy | Your Investment Property Australia

Protecting your privacy is important to Key Media Pty Ltd. We strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you are aware of and understand the Key Media Pty Ltd Customer Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service. Please take a moment to read the following policy to learn how we handle your personal information.

**Why we collect personal information**  
Key Media Pty Ltd collects and uses your personal information to give you superior customer service, to provide you with convenient access to our products and services, and to make a wider range available to you. In addition, we use your personal information to keep you up to date on the latest conferences/events and magazine announcements.

* * *

**How we collect personal information**  
We collect information about you in several ways. For example, we might ask for your contact information when you correspond with us, register to attend a conference or event. In addition, when you register for a new Key Media Pty Ltd conference, event or monthly update, we collect and store the information you provide in a secure database.

* * *

**When we disclose personal information**  
Because Key Media Pty Ltd is a global company, your personal information may be shared with other Key Media Pty Ltd business units in Australia, Canada, India, New Zealand, Singapore, Philippines, United Kingdom and USA. They will protect your personal information in accordance with the Key Media Pty Ltd Customer Privacy Policy. Key Media Pty Ltd may occasionally share your personal contact information with carefully selected partnering companies, to keep you informed about related announcements.

* * *

**How we protect your personal information**  
Key Media Pty Ltd safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

Key Media Pty Ltd does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information.

Key Media Pty Ltd's website contains links to other sites. Key Media Pty Ltd does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy policies of those companies.

If we are going to use your personal information differently from that stated at the time of collection, we will try to contact you via email using the most recent information we have. If you have not given us permission to communicate with you, you will not be contacted, nor will we use your personal information in a new manner.

The Key Media Pty Ltd Customer Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.

* * *

**Advertising**  
This website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.

* * *

**Control your personal data**  
You can remove from our email communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link present in the footer of all our email.

* * *

**Disclaimer**  
This information on this website is for general information purposes only. It is not intended as financial or investment advice and should not be construed or relied on as such. Before making any commitment of a financial nature you should seek advice from a qualified and registered financial or investment adviser. No material contained within this website should be construed or relied upon as providing recommendations in relation to any financial product. Key Media Pty Ltd does not recommend or endorse products and does not receive remuneration based upon investment decisions by our email recipients, publications, newsletter or website users.

* * *

**Questions about this policy or how Key Media Inc. handling of your information may be sent to:**

Key Media Inc  
Level 10, 1 Chandos St,   
St Leonards, NSW 2065   
Australia  
Phone: +61 2 8437 4700
